

Dang Quyet Tien

Full Stack Developer

Date of birth: Dec 04, 1991

Gender: Male

Phone: 0349.819.299

Email: quyettien.ictu@gmail.com

Address: Hanoi, Vietnam

Website: https://softviet.net

OBJECTIVE

I'm a software engineer with an appetite for complex problems. I'm easy going & take responsibility for my work. I would like to become a technical leader in the near future. So, over the last 5 years, I have developed a wide range of websites with many technologies such as Django, Reactjs, Nodejs, React Native, Kubernetes, Docker. They are including sites for startup companies and small businesses.

EDUCATION

Sep 2009 - July 2014 Information and Communications Technology University

Major: Software Technology

Degree: Good

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2017 - Present	MOBILE HEALTH - Team size: 6 members - Position: Backend Developer & DevOps Engineer
Feb 2018 - Sep 2018	FITi - Team size: 10 members - Position: Technical leader
June 2014 - 2017	SAMSUNG VIETNAM MOBILE CENTER (SVMC) - Team size: 15 members - Position: Backend developer and DevOps Engineer
Aug 2013 - Feb 2014	SOLID - Team size: 3 members - Position: Team leader
Aug 2012 - Aug 2013	DCOS - Team size: 8 members - Position: Developer

CERTIFICATIONS

2016	Software Technical Certificate - Advanced	
2013	Teaching Certificate	

SKILLS

Language	English, Vietnames	
Programing Language	Python (Django), C#, React.js, React Native, NodeJs (Sails.js)	
DevOps	Git, Perforce, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Docker, Microservice, Ansible, Terraform, Packer, Fastlane, Fabric	

INTERESTS

I like to explore new technologies

PROJECTS

Uptra - Cross Promotion

(2019 - 2019)

Customer	Vala
Description	a Shopify application.
Team size	5
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Develop API for the client application
Technologies used	- React Js, Sails.js, Docker

Busio by FITi

(2018 - 2018)

Customer	FITi
Description	a Shopify application.
Team size	5
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Develop API for the client application
Technologies used	- React Js, Sails.js, Docker

Chatative by FITi

(2018 - 2018)

Customer	FITi
Description	a Shopify application.
Team size	5
My position	Team leader & Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Develop API for the client application
Technologies used	- React Js, Django, Docker

Manadr

(2017 - 2018)

Customer	Mobile Health	
Description	This app allows patient connect to doctors.	

Team size	25	
My position	Backend Developer & DevOps Engineer	
My responsibilities	 - Develop APIs for the mobile application - Develop a mobile application in React Native - Design microservice architecture - Setup CI/CD system with Jenkins, Kubernetes, AWS, Ansible, Terraform, Packer, Fabric and Fastlane 	
Technologies used	- Python, Django, React Js, React Native, Docker	

SUPER ENGLISH

(2017 - 2017)

Customer	ICRARY
Description	Learn English online
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Analysis and designDevelopmentReview codeOptimize codeBug Fixing
Technologies used	- Python, Django

RETRIEVER

(2/2016 - 7/2017)

Customer	SAMSUNG MOBILE CENTER	
Description	This is the system that helps project leader manage project very good.	
Team size	5	
My position	Developer	
My responsibilities	 - Analysis and design - Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing 	
Technologies used	- Django, React.js	

AUTOPOST

(2014 - 2014)

Customer	SOLID
Description	The software automatically posted ads
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design - Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- C#

AUTO SCAN EMAIL, MOBILE NUMBER

(2013 - 2014)

Customer	SOLID	
----------	-------	--

Description	This is app can collect all mobile number, email address from any website.
Team size	2
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design - Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	C#

RESTAURANT MANAGEMENT

(2012 - 2013)

Customer	DCOS
Description	This is app that helps manager restaurant easy.
Team size	8
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	C#, Asp.net